{
    "id": "849b68eea1624010b504fc37238a063e",
    "title": "Simple, Complex vs. Compound",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "aa5c372ec8ac499a8513a828e6372c29",
            "title": "Simple, Complex vs. Compound",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "That was a sight to behold.",
                    "description": "A simple sentence has just one clause and one finite verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have invited all of my friends to my party.",
                    "description": "A simple sentence has just one clause and one finite verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "What she said didn’t make much sense to me.",
                    "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I invited her but she didn’t come.",
                    "description": "A compound sentence has two or more coordinate clauses of the same rank.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you got any idea what you have done?",
                    "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It took me ten minutes to get ready.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t need your permission to go.",
                    "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He asked me if I was interested in the offer.",
                    "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "As I had some work to do, I didn’t go to the movies.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was worried because he was guilty.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She asked me where I had been.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can wait or you can leave.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex",
                        "Compound"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}